This is a work of fiction.
Underage drinking is strongly prohibited and illegal.
Scenes involving alcohol with forceful consumption
and shameful acts are not encouraged.
Please view this as a comedy.
Furthermore, all characters appearing
in this work are of legal age.
Chisa, I beg you. Stay by my side.
（伊織(いおり)）千紗(ちさ) 頼む
俺のそばにいてくれ
No.
（千紗）イヤ
I'm not asking anything else of you.
何かをしてほしいなんて言わない
Just stay by my side.
ただ そばにいてくれるだけで
十分なんだ
No way. Give up already.
絶対にイヤ 諦めて
（伊織）ああ…
No...
そんな…
I only want you to sit next to me
and let me see your answers!
隣で回答を見せてくれるだけで
いいんだ！
（伊織の泣き声）
（千紗）フン…
-Sorry, I couldn't get her to help us cheat.
-I see.
（伊織）すまん
カンニング交渉は失敗だ
（耕平(こうへい)）そうか…
What are we going to do? We're going to fail.
（野島(のじま)）どうすっか
このままだと不可だ
I don't want to fail German.
（山本(やまもと)）ドイツ語の
単位を落とすのは痛いぞ
Nothing we can do.
We'll have to help ourselves.
しかたがない
自力でなんとかしよう
Are you serious?
You're going to start studying now?
まさか 今から勉強するのか？
There's no time before the test.
試験まで時間がないぞ
I'm going to see how small I can photocopy my notes.
ノートの縮小コピーの
限界に挑戦する
You're going to help yourself cheat.
（耕平）自力のカンニングか
This is the smallest that I can still read.
（伊織）これが 字の読める
限界サイズだな
It's pretty small.
だいぶ小さくなったな…
We have to think of where to hide it.
隠す場所を考える必要があるな
Kitahara! Cheating, huh?
Let me in on it!
（御手洗(みたらい)）北原(きたはら)
カンニングか？　俺もまぜてくれ
Me too! Me too!
（藤原(ふじわら)）俺も俺も
Why do I always attract such losers?
なぜ 俺の周りには
こんなクズばかりが集まるんだ？
Birds of a feather flock together.
（耕平）類友ってやつだろ
So how will we conceal it?
（山本）
んで これをどう持ち込む？
Well...
（伊織）そうだな…
For example, in my pencil box.
METHOD 1: A PENCIL BOX
Under my drink label.
（山本）飲み物のラベル
METHOD 2: A DRINK LABEL
Inside my towel.
（耕平）タオルの内側
METHOD 3: A TOWEL
うむ… 野島はどうする？
How about you, Nojima?
I'm going to do a "wannai"!
俺はワンナイでいく
One night? You're going to pull an all-nighter?
ワンナイト… 一夜漬けか？
No. I'll put it in my arm!
（野島）いや 腕内だ
-What are you going to do, Kitahara?
-I'm going to put it on the back of my fan.
（山本）北原はどうするんだ？
俺は… うちわの裏かな
（藤原）なら俺は 服に仕込むか
I'll hide it in my clothes.
You guys know it's important to pass German, right?
お前ら ドイツ語の単位が
重要なのは知ってるな？
-Yeah!
-Of course!
（耕平）ああ！
（山本）もちろんだとも！
We're not giving up!
絶対に最後まで諦めず
みんなで単位を取るぞ！
We're all going to pass together!
Yeah!
（一同）おおー！
Okay. Well then...
（講師）はい それでは―
First, put away your pencil boxes.
まず 筆箱はしまいなさい
（御手洗）えっ…
（山本）フフフ… バカめ
予想できたことだろ
Idiot. You should've seen that coming.
（御手洗）おい 助けてくれ
Hey! Help me!
（山本）ん～ どうしよっかな
I don't know...
And no eating or drinking.
（講師）それと 飲食は禁止です
Don't look at me like that!
（伊織）
そんな目でこっちを見んな！
Do something!
（野島）てめえでなんとかしろ！
How come everyone else looks so calm?
（伊織）しかし なぜほかの連中は
涼しい顔をしてられるんだ？
Do they have confidence in themselves?
（耕平）
まさか 自信があるとか？
The test starts at 1:00.
１時開始です
終わったら退席してかまいません
You can leave if you finish early.
Begin.
では 始め
I'm leaving.
（２人）退席します
I see. They already made their decision.
（伊織）
覚悟を決めた笑みだったか…
（野島）ううっ！
The letters smudged from my sweat! I can't read it!
（野島）汗でにじんで
文字が読めねえ…
Idiot.
（耕平）バカが
（伊織）フッ… この暑さで
ワンナイに頼るからだ
It's because you used your arm when it's so hot.
（耕平）そういえば
下川(しもかわ)がいないな
Shimokawa isn't here.
Yeah. Just now, he...
（伊織）ああ やつならさっき…
（メッセージの受信音）
I'LL START STUDYING NOW.
TELL ME WHAT'S ON TOMORROW'S TEST.
（伊織）ハァ…
NO NEED TO KNOW ANYMORE.
Just now?
さっき なんだ？
Don't worry about it.
One more person died. That's all.
（伊織）気にするな
死人が１人 増えただけだ
But...
（伊織）しかし…
カンペを見てもほとんど解けん
My cheat sheet isn't helping at all.
We have to help each other.
（耕平）これは みんなで
協力する必要があるな
It's teamwork time.
（山本）チームプレーだな
Leave it to me.
（藤原）任しとけ！
This work is an original copyrighted material
of the Content Provider. Unauthorized reproduction
or distribution of this work in any form or manner
is prohibited. Some viewers might find this work disturbing
as it may contain strong language, a degree of violence
or adult situations. Viewer discretion is advised.
Please watch it at your own risk.
The story, names, characters and incidents portrayed
in this work are fictitious. No identification with actual
persons, organizations, religions, places and products
is intended. The Content Provider, the producers
and related parties shall have no liability,
as to the accuracy, legality, safety or suitability
for any purpose of the information provided in this work.
The views and opinions expressed herein do not reflect
the views and opinions of the Content Provider,
or any of its affiliates, partners, subsidiaries, or Licensee.
What's this?
これは 何かね？
うう…
I thought we were helping each other!
みんなで協力は!?
FAIL
フゥ…
みんな出来が悪いなあ…
Everyone's doing poorly on the test.
The questions are too hard.
問題が難しすぎるんだよ
It can't be helped. I'll give you a freebie.
しかたがない
サービス問題を出そう
Really?
（学生たち）おおっ！
I covered this in class.
講義中の話から出題します
Translate what I'm about to say into German
and write it on the back.
今から言う単語をドイツ語に訳して
裏面に書きなさい
Question 1:
第１問 “心臓リウマチ”
"Rheumatoid arthritis."
（伊織）分かるか んなもん…
How should I know?
Someone, tell him what "freebie" means!
（耕平）サービスの意味を
誰か教えてやれ！
Question 2:
第２問
"A man holding a banana while naked."
“裸でバナナを持つ男”
What was he talking about in class?
（山本）講義中に
なんの話をしていた!?
Is this really a German class?
（藤原）本当に
ドイツ語の講義なのか!?
The last question.
最後の１問
"James Thomas."
“ジェームス トーマス”
（伊織）人名じゃねえか！
A name?
（耕平）
しかも 明らかに英語だろ！
And it's obviously English!
I can't deal with this anymore!
（野島）やってられっか！
This is terrible.
これはひどい…
We definitely failed.
不可確定か…
We have to make up for this somehow.
どこかで挽回しないと
Everyone, you all did very poorly.
（講師）えー 皆さん
大変 出来が悪かったです
So if you get over 10 points, you pass,
なので 10点以上なら可
20点以上なら良とします
and if you get over 20, you get an A.
Seriously?
（３人）マジで!?
Great! I didn't think we'd do it!
やったな！
まさか いけるとは！
Right? That saved us!
だな 助かった！
Yeah. Definitely!
ああ まったくだ！　ん？
A retake?
（伊織）再試？　チクショー！
No!
（耕平･伊織･野島）ああ～
They're acting stupid again.
またバカやってる…
Be passionate, my friends
♪～
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
GRAND BLUE DREAMING
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
An expanding ocean of possibilities
Summer is our amore
We'll swear to the crystal clear sky
Summer is in our hands
Be passionate, my friends
Shine bright with the sun
Dive into the blue sky
And let summer take it all
With a cheerful heart
Don't mess with me
Keep going even if you fall
And let summer take it all
～♪
（寿(ことぶき)）で 合コンは
どうだったんだ？
So how was the mixer?
It was terrible Look at this photo.
さんざんでしたよ
見てください！　この写真
こいつら 仮装してきやがって
-They came dressed in costumes.
-We went all out! You should be grateful.
（愛菜(あいな)）気合い入れて
あげたんだから 感謝しなさいよ
You guys never disappoint.
（梓(あずさ)）君らは期待を裏切らないねえ
By the way, you said you wanted to join our club.
ところで お前
うちに入るっていうけどさ
Do you know what club this is?
なんのサークルか知ってるのか？
Diving, right?
I wanted to try it out.
ダイビングでしょ？
ちょっと憧れてたのよね
It's such a grown-up hobby.
大人の趣味って感じで
I'm interested in what's in the ocean and in colorful fish.
海の中も 色とりどりの魚にも
興味があるし
Great.
それはそれは…
Going diving with college friends on a tropical island!
南の島のきれいな海で
大学の仲間とダイビング！
It's like a drama on TV!
まるで ドラマみたいじゃない？
Then you shouldn't join this club.
（耕平･伊織）
なら このサークルはやめておけ
Isn't this is a diving club?
（愛菜）ここ
ダイビングサークルじゃないの？
ハハッ 冗談だ 冗談
Just kidding.
ダイビングをすることも
ないわけじゃないが―
It's not that we never dive,
but I feel like we never dive.
ない気がしなくもないぞ
Hey, new member!
Your welcome party is starting!
（時田(ときた)）おーい 新入り！
歓迎会 始めんぞ！
（愛菜）あっ はい！
Okay!
Well, introduce yourself.
（寿）じゃあ 自己紹介だ
I'm Aina Yoshiwara, a freshman from OWU!
青海(おうみ)女子１年の 吉原(よしわら)愛菜です
（一同）おお～！
I'm interested in diving,
but I've never tried it before.
ダイビングに興味はあったのですが
やったことはないです
（一同）おお～！
Starting now, I want to learn lots and--
なので これから
いろいろ勉強をし…
ヒッ！
このサークル おかしくない？
Isn't this club weird?
（伊織）ん？
（愛菜）いつの間に脱いだの？
You took your clothes off!
Don't be so surprised.
（伊織）そう驚かれてもな
You already got a good look
at the Izu Spring Festival.
伊豆(いず)春祭(はるさい)で飲んでるとき
さんざん見ただろ
So you weren't just letting loose after the festival?
あれって 学祭でテンション
振り切ってたからじゃないんだ？
What's wrong, Aina?
（梓）どうしたの？　愛菜
（愛菜）どうしたも何も…
Everything's wrong!
（梓）ん？
（愛菜）なんでもないです…
It's nothing.
But at least Kotegawa is supposed to be normal.
（愛菜）で でも…
古手川(こてがわ)さんだけは普通の人のはず
Please, Kotegawa! You're the only one
who can set up a mixer!
（耕平）頼む！　古手川！
（伊織）やっぱりお前が合コンを！
No, Chisa. I didn't mean I want you to sit on top of me.
違うぞ 千紗
上に座ってくれって意味じゃない
-Did you want me to step on you?
-Or not...
踏めばよかった？
でもないな…
What are you two doing?
（奈々華(ななか)）
２人とも 何をしてるの？
Nothing.
（千紗）別に…
（伊織）奈々華さん
Nanaka.
（奈々華）ほら 千紗ちゃん
伊織君から降りて
Hey, Chisa-chan. Get off of Iori.
Great! I'm glad there's someone normal here!
よかった！
普通の人がいてくれた！
Thank you.
お疲れさまです
Nanaka, how about a drink?
（伊織）奈々華さんも
１杯どうですか？
Thanks. Okay.
（奈々華）ありがとう それじゃ…
I'll have this.
これ もらうね
Kotegawa was drinking that...
（愛菜）えっ それは
古手川さんの飲みかけ…
（奈々華）はむっ
（愛菜）わっ！　うっ…
（奈々華）アハッ…
Hey...
（愛菜）ねえ…
（伊織）何も聞くな
Don't ask.
お前は何も見ていない
いいな？
You didn't see anything. Got that?
Hey, you guys!
（時田）コラァ！　お前ら
（伊織）うう…
You have to give a toast!
きちんと乾杯しないと
ダメじゃないか！
（伊織･耕平）う… うわあ！
（愛菜）あっ ちょっ…
Hold on--
Yoshiwara...
（千紗）あの 吉原さん
（愛菜）は… はい
Yes?
Are you interested in diving?
（千紗）ダイビングに興味あるの？
Yeah. I guess.
う… うん 一応
それが何か？
-Why?
-No...
（千紗）いや 別に
なんでもないんだけど
It's nothing...
I was just glad.
うれしいなって…
Right.
そうよね
You're the only person who joined
because you were interested.
（梓）素直に興味を持って
入会したのは愛菜だけだもんね
は はあ…
So, what equipment do I need to get for diving?
ところで ダイビングって何を
用意しておいたらいいんですか？
う～ん そうねえ
Well...
There's a lot.
いろいろあるんだけど…
Just renting is fine in the beginning.
（梓）最初はレンタルで
いいんじゃないかな
For starters, a towel and swimsuit.
とりあえずは
タオルとか水着かしら
A swimsuit?
み… 水着ですか？
You don't like swimsuits?
水着はイヤ？
It's not that I don't like them.
It's just embarrassing...
イヤというか… 恥ずかしくて
フフッ 大丈夫よ
You'll be fine!
（梓）恥ずかしいことなんて
なんもないって
There's nothing embarrassing about it.
That's because you are all used to diving.
それは 皆さんが
ダイビングに慣れてるからで―
For normal people--
普通の人は…
（梓）ん？
Yeah! Yeah!
（部員たち）
ワッショイ！　ワッショイ！
There's no one normal here!
（愛菜）普通の人が
どこにもいない…
（奈々華･千紗･梓）ん？
（千紗）大丈夫？
Are you okay?
Anyway, today is my welcome party!
（愛菜）とにかく！
今日は私の歓迎会なんだから―
So, everyone, put your clothes on!
みんな 服を着てくださ～い！
（時田）ん～？
（伊織）どうしました？
What's wrong?
We're out of booze.
酒が切れた
（耕平）ええっ!?
（梓）１本もないの？
Not even one bottle left?
I estimated wrong.
数を見誤ったなあ
No way. You're a veteran.
（伊織）そんな
先輩ともあろう人が…
Then I'll go buy some.
じゃあ 私 買ってきます
It's going to be heavy. We'll go.
重いだろう 俺たちが行くぞ
It's okay, the store's really close.
いいですよ
コンビニ近いですし
Then I'll go too.
あ… じゃあ 私も
I'm going now!
（愛菜）じゃあ いってきまーす
（梓）はいはーい
Okay!
Make sure you put on your clothes.
ちゃんと
服 着ててくださいね
Okay.
はいはーい
（伊織）フゥ…
あいつも早く慣れないとな
She better get used to this soon.
Yeah.
（耕平）まったくだ
Though, you two got used to this way too soon.
（梓）２人は
慣れるの早すぎだけどね
Hey, who bought the bamboo shoots
instead of the mushrooms?
おいおい 誰だよ
きのこと間違えて
たけのこを買ったのは
は？　何言ってるんだ？
What are you talking about?
The bamboo shoots are better.
普通は きのこより
たけのこだろ
You're kidding me.
冗談はよせよ　たけのこなんて
味覚音痴の食べ物だろうが
Bamboo shoots are for people with no sense of taste.
No, no!
いやいや きのここそが
バカ舌の食べ物だろ！
Mushrooms are for people with bad taste!
Hey! What did you just say?
おい コラ！　なんて言った！
You can't even tell the difference
between a cracker and a cookie!
クラッカーとクッキーの
味の差も分からん味音痴が！
Haven't you ever compared their sales?
ああ？
売り上げ比較したことねえのか？
You bastard! This means war!
てめえ！　それを言ったら
もう戦争だろうが！
ああ？　やんのか コラァ！
Want to fight?
Hey, wait. Stop fighting!
待て待て
（寿）ケンカはいかんぞ ケンカは
（伊織･耕平）ですが！
-But!
I thought I already told you,
you should solve things with a game.
こういうときは ゲームでと
前に言っただろうが
いいでしょう
All right.
なんのゲームで
勝負したらいいんですか？
What should we play?
Well...
（寿）そうだなあ…
（時田）あみだで決めるか
Let's use a Ghost Leg.
Tokki, Bukki, think of some games.
じゃあ トッキーとブッキーは
ゲームの案 出して
Okay. Have you picked one?
（時田）よし 選んだな
（伊織･耕平）はい
Yeah.
（寿）それじゃ 結果はっと…
And the result is...
The Pocky game.
ポッチーゲームだな
-What in the world?
（伊織･耕平）
なっ！　なんてものを！
Hold on!
（伊織）ちょっ…
ちょっと待ってくださいよ
Who's idea was this?
誰の案ですか こんな… えっ？
ク～！
Azusa!
梓さ～ん！
This is your chance.
チャンス チャンス！
You guys settle this with a Pocky game!
んじゃ ポッチーゲームで
決着をつけてもらうぞ
No, no, no!
（伊織）いやいやいや！
（耕平）おかしいですって！
This is wrong!
There's nothing wrong!
おかしくない おかしくない
It's the result of the sacred Ghost Leg. Just accept it.
神聖な あみだの結果だ
諦めろ
We don't have any Pocky.
でも ポッチーがないですし
So we can't play.
やりたくても できませんし
（時田）ふむ…
（梓）確かにないねえ
You're right.
Then let's use this.
なら これを使うか…
It's kind of big, but it'll work.
ちょっと でかいが
なんとかなんだろう
The first person who takes their mouth off loses.
先に口を離したほうが負けな
Ready, set, go!
んじゃ 用意 スタート！
（耕平･伊織）フガフガ…
This looks worse than I imagined.
想像以上にひどい絵面だな
We can't let Chii-chan and Aina see this.
ちーちゃんたちには
見せられないねえ
（耕平･伊織）ハァ ハァ…
There's no winner.
（時田）決着つかずか…
A tie? Too bad.
（寿）引き分けとは だらしがない
いや これは無理ですよ
This is impossible.
It's killing my mouth.
口の中 大変なことに
なるんですからね
Too bad.
しかたないなあ…
Azusa, what's your idea?
（伊織）梓さん 何を？
I thought I'd get some Pocky.
ポッチーを用意しようと思ってね
（メッセージの受信音）
Azusa says buy some Pocky.
（千紗）梓さんが
“ポッチーを買ってきて”だって
Pocky?
（愛菜）ポッチー？
（千紗）甘いものなんて珍し…
Sweets? That's weird.
IORI AND KOHEI WANT TO PLAY THE POCKY GAME
（愛菜･千紗）ん…
What happened while we've been gone?
目を離した間に何が…
You guys are enjoying this, aren't you?
ていうか 先輩たち
楽しんでますよね！
Why don't you guys participate too?
それなら 先輩たちにも
参加してもらいますよ！
Well...
まあ なあ…
I'm okay with that.
別にいいけど
I don't mind.
俺もかまわんが
How are we going to choose who plays who?
だが ゲームをする２人を
どう選ぶ？
そ… それは…
Well...
With Rock, Paper, Scissors or something.
まあ ジャンケンか何かで
（時田）そうか～
（寿）ジャンケンとなると…
I see!
That means...
（梓）はいはい～ 了解！
All right! I get it!
We're back.
（千紗）ただいま
（愛菜）買ってきましたよ
We bought--
Out! Safe! Yeah!
（一同）アウト！　セーフ！
よよいの！
Welcome back!
あっ おかえり～
Why do you always end up like this?
（愛菜）
どうしてそうなるんですか！
Wait, Cakey! There's a good reason!
待て ケバ子
これには わけがある
We were just playing Rock, Paper, Scissors
to decide who plays the Pocky game!
俺たちは
ポッチーゲームをするために―
まず ジャンケンを
していただけなんだ
You don't have to strip
to play Rock, Paper, Scissors!
ジャンケンするだけなら
脱ぐ必要ないでしょ！
-This is naked Rock, Paper, Scissors. We have to strip.
-That's right.
野球拳なんだから―
脱ぐ必要があるだろ
（寿）まったくだ
（愛菜）野球拳以外の
ジャンケンも覚えなさいよ！
Learn how to play Rock, Paper, Scissors
without stripping!
In other words, like normal?
要するに…
いつもどおりですか
This is normal.
いつもどおりだねえ…
Anyway...
（寿）しかし なんだなあ
We got more new members,
so it's time to get ready for the license class.
新入生も増えたし―
いよいよ ライセンス講習の
準備を始めるか
You're right.
あ～ そうだな
（耕平）はあ
License?
ライセンスですか
それって 早脱ぎの？
For who can strip fastest?
It's for who drinks fastest.
早飲みに決まってんだろ
Why do you think that?
どうしてそうなる？
It's for diving, of course.
ダイビングに決まってんだろ
-Diving?
（伊織･耕平）ダイビング!?
No way!
そんな バカな！
（伊織）ううっ…
Is it our fault they're acting like that?
この反応は 俺たちが悪いのか？
I think it's half-half.
俺は半々だと思うが
I have to ask you...
一応 聞くが―
You looked at the textbook, right?
お前ら 教本には
目を通してあるんだろうな
Of course.
そりゃあ もちろん
（耕平）聞くまでもなく…
No need to ask.
They haven't looked at it.
こいつら 絶対
目を通してないな
Let's give them a quiz.
ひとつ テストしてみるか
（時田）うん
Do you guys know the hand signals?
２人とも
ハンドシグナルは知っているか？
-Yes.
-They're gestures, right?
はい
要は ジェスチャーですよね
They're important signals
for communicating underwater.
水中での意思疎通に使う
重要なサインだ
I'm going to do them right now.
（時田）今から俺が
実際にやってみせる
Watch, and think about what I'm trying to say.
それを見て
何を訴えてるか考えてみろ
Stop.
Look this way.
I'm going to dive.
（伊織）ふむ… つまり…
In other words...
Stop right there.
I'm...
going to kill you.
Okay, Iori. What are you supposed to do next?
さて 伊織
お前はどうしたらいい？
（伊織）ふむ…
I'm going to shoot him first with an underwater gun.
相手より先に
水中銃で撃ちます
What's going on?
（耕平）どういう状況なんだ？
We can't use hand signals with Iori.
うかつに伊織の前で
ハンドシグナルは使えんな
It's Kohei's turn next.
（時田）次 耕平の番な
You'll see how much better I am than Kitahara.
俺と北原の違いを
見せてやりますよ
Keep your mouth shut, dimwit.
ほざくな ボケナス
A problem has occurred.
"Yahoo"?
No more air.
"Aiin"?
I'm going to go up.
"Yeah, yeah."
How was it, Kohei?
どうだ？　耕平
I'm going to watch over you!
俺は 温かい目で見守るぞ
What a bizarre idea.
猟奇的な発想だな
You didn't study after all.
やっぱり勉強していなかったか…
-Sorry.
（伊織･耕平）すいません…
Well, I already knew that.
まあ 分かっていたことだがな
Anyway...
というわけで 少しは勉強してみろ
Try studying a bit.
（伊織）今からですか？
Now?
Something good might happen once you memorize it.
（寿）覚えたら 意外と
いいことがあるかもしれないぞ？
（伊織･耕平）はあ…
（伊織）うーん…
Iori, are you studying for your license?
伊織君 ライセンスのお勉強？
Yes. Just the hand signals, though.
はい…
ハンドシグナルだけですが
へえ～ どれどれ？
Let me see.
（伊織）うっ！
こ… この感触は…
This feels like...
You should memorize these first.
まずは ここから覚えるといいよ
Good things really do happen.
（伊織）まさか 本当に
いいことが起こるとは…
Hand signals are wonderful!
なんて すばらしいんだ
ハンドシグナル！
Oh, by the way, Iori...
あ… そういえば 伊織君
Yes?
（伊織）はっ はい
I heard something just now.
さっき こんな話を聞いたんだけど
知ってる？
Know anything about it?
（伊織）なんの話ですか？
What do you mean?
I heard that you're going out with Chisa-chan.
伊織君と千紗ちゃんが
おつきあいしてるって話…
Oh, the signals are coming in handy!
（時田）
おっ さっそく役に立っているな
That signal means "a problem has occurred."
（耕平）あのサインは
“問題発生”ですね
Yeah. It's an important signal.
（寿）ああ 重要なサインの１つだ
What's wrong?
どうしたのさ
Azusa, it's an emergency.
梓さん 緊急事態です
Nanaka heard about it.
奈々華さんが
例の話を知ってしまったようで
（梓）ああ…
（伊織）なんとかなりませんか？
Can you do anything to help?
Okay, leave it to me.
（梓）オッケー　私に任せなさい！
You're the best, Azusa!
I can always count on you!
（伊織）
さすが梓さん 頼もしい！
What are you going to do?
ちなみに
どうするつもりなんですか？
Don't worry about it.
別に 大したことしないよ
I'm just going to tell her
who you really like.
伊織が本当に好きな子は誰か
教えてくるだけ！
（伊織）えっ！
（梓）おっ…
いやあ 俺は千紗が大好きだな！
Well, I do really love Chisa!
ハハハ…
You like digging your own grave.
（梓）伊織はつくづく
墓穴を掘るのが好きだねえ…
Iori...
（奈々華）い… おり… くん！
うわあっ！
That one means "come here."
（耕平）そして あれは
“こっちに来てください”ですか…
Iori is learning them by using them.
（時田）伊織は実践して
どんどん覚えてんな
Don't let him beat you, Kohei.
耕平も負けていられないぞ
Nanaka, just now, that was--
あのですね 奈々華さん
今のは その…
Good!
よかった！
え？
It seemed like you guys weren't getting along recently,
so I was worried.
このところ ２人の仲が
険悪みたいだから 心配だったの
But if that's what you say, everything's fine.
でも 伊織君がそうなら
大丈夫よね
（伊織）はあ…
（梓）奈々華 いいの？
Nanaka, are you okay with this?
えっ 何が？
What?
だってほら
ちーちゃんと伊織が…
You know Chii-chan and Iori are...?
It's a good thing, right?
いいことじゃない！
They get along so well
that they look like they're going out.
おつきあいしてるように
見えるくらい 仲がいいんでしょ？
What a convenient interpretation.
（伊織）
なんという ご都合的解釈！
ふうん… そうじゃなくて
本当につきあってるとしたら？
What if they really were going out?
（伊織）うっ！
（奈々華）うーん…
ウフフ…
ちょっと分からないかな
I'm not really sure.
Right?
いやあ ですよねえ
-Azusa's question makes no sense!
-No...
まったく 梓さんの質問は
全然意味が分からなくて…
ううん そうじゃなくて
No, that's not it.
I mean I'm not really sure what I'd do.
自分が何をするか
分からないかな…
I might get killed someday.
（伊織）俺 そのうち
殺されるかもしれん…
Don't worry!
大丈夫ですよ
そんなこと ありえませんから
That would never happen!
Right. They haven't been getting along recently.
そうそう 最近
むしろ険悪なくらいだし
Since I'm her older sister, I can't just ignore it.
それはそれで 姉としては―
見過ごせないのよね
（伊織）はあ…
Then let's do this for tomorrow's practice.
それじゃ 明日の練習は
こうしましょ　ウフッ
Okay. We're going to have you dive in pairs today.
（奈々華）はい 今日は
それぞれのペアで潜ってもらいます
What? This is awkward.
（伊織）何これ？　居心地悪い…
Let's change into swimsuits first.
それじゃあ まず
水着に着替えましょうか
（愛菜）ええっ!?
（耕平）じゃ 着替えますか…
Let's change.
You're changing here?
ここで着替えるの!?
Why do you care now?
いまさら気にすることもないだろ
That's not what I'm talking about.
そういう問題じゃない
わあっ！
２人とも何してるんです!?
What are you two doing?
（奈々華）え？
（梓）着替えてるんだけど？
We're changing.
In front of other people?
（愛菜）人前なのに？
うっ… 古手川さん
何か言って… えっ!?
Kotegawa, say something!
We have swimsuits on already.
It's no big deal.
下に水着 着てるなら別に…
That's right.
そうだよ
Yours looks like underwear.
梓のは下着みたいだけどね
Blushing because of your bathing suit?
So innocent.
水着で てれるとは…
初々しいな
Yup.
まったくだな
You guys could act a little more innocent, you know.
先輩方は もうちょい
初々しくてもいいんですけどね
I've had enough of these people!
（愛菜）この人たち もうイヤ！
Nanaka...
（伊織）奈々華さん
（奈々華）何？　伊織君
What, Iori?
Why is Chisa paired up with me?
どうして 俺と千紗が
ペアなんですか？
I wanted you guys to make up.
２人に
仲直りしてもらおうと思って
It'll have the opposite effect.
（伊織）むしろ 逆効果のような…
It'll be okay.
Chii-chan is easy when she's in the ocean.
（梓）大丈夫よ
ちーちゃんって 海に入れば―
すごく ちょろい子だから
（奈々華）そうねえ
Right.
（伊織）それ 本人が聞いたら
すっげえ怒りますよ
If she heard that, she'd be mad.
Okay, Iori, don't get far away from me.
じゃあ 伊織
私から離れないようにね
お… おう
Okay.
（千紗）どうしたの 伊織
不安？
What's wrong, Iori?
Are you nervous?
え？　ああ いや…
No...
We're just going to swim somewhere shallow today.
今日は すごく浅いところで
泳ぐだけだから―
If you're scared, don't push yourself.
Tell me if anything's wrong.
怖かったら無理しないで
何かあったらすぐ教えて
Okay. Got it.
お… おう　分かった
Okay, I can do it.
（伊織）よし いける
シャレが通じる空気じゃないな…
This isn't the time for jokes...
（伊織）あれ？　千紗のやつ―
Chisa's not mad.
怒っているっていうより
何か…
Instead, she's...
Oh, right.
ああ そうか…
She's just being serious.
あいつは ただ
真剣なだけなんだ
To make sure an accident doesn't happen.
万が一にも
事故が起きないように
So that we can enjoy
being underwater.
できるかぎり
水の中を楽しめるように
For me, since I'm scared of the water.
水が苦手な俺のために
That was really fun!
すっごい楽しかった！
It looks like you enjoyed it.
気に入ってくれたようだね
（愛菜）はい！
Yes!
よかった～
Good.
（伊織）ハァ…
Did you have fun, Iori?
伊織は楽しかった？
Yeah. Of course.
ああ もちろんだ
そう…
Good.
よかった
あ…
-They made up.
-Yeah.
やっぱり 仲直りできた
（梓）うん
Everything's okay now.
Well, still, you really are Nanaka's little sister.
いやあ それにしても
さすがは奈々華さんの妹だな
何が？
What?
後ろから見ていて
思ったんだが―
I knew it when I saw you from behind.
You have a spectacular ass.
尻のラインが
大変 見事だった
ああっ… うう…
Die twenty thousand times!
２万回 死ね！
（伊織）あっ！
（海に落ちる音）
DEEP BLUE AL FINE
KAYA MIZUKI
Here's your mic, Kitahara.
（耕平）ほれ 北原 マイク
（伊織）俺もかよ
Me, too...? All right, let's do this!
よっしゃ いくぜ！
-Yeah, sing your heart out.
-You guys seem to be having fun.
（寿）おお～ 歌え歌え！
（時田）ノリノリだな
A fairytale whispers
In a fake world
♪～
Hiding in the complete darkness
I reach for the forbidden fruit
In my last days
Now I know the meaning of the song about hope
A broken gear will never stop again
Even if I were to lose everything
I'd still want you to know
Trapped in the sky so far away
I'm praying with ripped off wings
Because we span together
The vows of areppegio
If life sparkles only to the beat
of the resonating stars
I'll sacrifice everything
Till death do us apart
Cheers!
～♪
Thank you!
（一同）サンキュー！
-We're going to have a tennis doubles match!
-Hold on!
（２人）テニスで
ダブルスの試合を行う
（耕平･伊織）ちょい待てや！
-You're not dressed as a girl this time.
-It's come to this.
（工藤(くどう)）今回は
女装していないんだね
（伊織）こうなったら もう…
We have no choice.
（耕平）もう
俺たちに残された手は…
（伊織･耕平）ＫＯしかない！
A knockout!
NEXT EPISODE
"DOUBLES"